biggerbolderbaking.com 2019-04-19

# Bigger Bolder Baking Website Privacy Policy - Gemma’s Bigger Bolder Baking

**Bigger Bolder Baking**

**Privacy Policy**

Welcome to BiggerBolderBaking.com (the “Site”). Taste Buds Entertainment LLC (the “Company”, “we”, or “us”) values your privacy and security and provides this Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) to describe the ways in which we may collect, use, and share your personal information. By using or accessing the Site in any way, whether or not you register as a user (a “User”), you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

We may revise this Privacy Policy at any time by updating this document. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will be posted on the Site under the link “Privacy Policy.” Every time you access the Site you agree to be bound by the current Privacy Policy as posted.

**LAST MODIFIED: MAY 25, 2018**

**1\. Our Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

We use cookies for the following purposes:

(a) authentication – we use cookies to identify you when you visit our website and as you navigate our website;

(b) status – we use cookies [to help us to determine if you are logged into our website;

(c) personalization – we use cookies to store information about your preferences and to personalize the website for you;

(d) security – we use cookies as an element of the security measures used to protect user accounts, including preventing fraudulent use of login credentials, and to protect our website and services generally;

(e) advertising – we use cookies to help us to display advertisements that will be relevant to you; and

(f) analysis – we use cookies to help us to analyze the use and performance of our website and services;

We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google’s privacy policy is available at: [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:

(a) [https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en) (Chrome);

(b) [https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)(Firefox);

(c) [http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/](http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/) (Opera);

(d) [https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies](https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies) (Internet Explorer);

(e) [https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411) (Safari); and

(f) [https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy) (Edge).

Please note that blocking cookies may have a negative impact on the functions of many websites, including our Site. Some features of the Site may cease to be available to you.

**2\. Information we Collect  **

  1. We may collect, store, and use the below personal information from you when you access or visit the Site: 
    1. **Information we automatically collect.** This includes information about your browser, computer or mobile device, and interaction with the Site. We generally collect this through the use of cookies, which are small text files placed on your computer. Cookies do not give us access to your computer but help us optimize the Site experience for you. We may also obtain this information by using clear .gif files, log files, or other tracking devices.
    2. **User account registration information.** This includes any information you voluntarily submit to the Site when you register a User account, including your name, email address, and other contact and profile information.
    3. **User Content and other information you submit to the Site.** The Site allows members to submit User Content, as that term is defined in the Terms of Use. We will collect all User Content you submit.
    4. **Information you submit when contacting the Company**. If you contact the Company through email, social media, or a contact form, we will collect the information you submit.
    5. **Information collected by advertisers**. Third party advertisers, including Google, may use cookies (small text files that track your browsing history) to serve ads based on your browsing history or interests. For Google based ads, you may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Ads Settings portion of your Google account.

**3\. How we Share and Use Personal Information**

We generally use personal information in order to improve the Site and to provide new and unique content submitted by Users. In particular:

  1. We may share User Content as provided for in the license described in the Terms of Use posted on the Site. This includes derivatives of the User Content. When sharing User Content, we may also include your public User account information.
  2. If you create a User account we may use that information to send you messages about the Site or products we think would be useful to you. You may opt out of Site emails by following the unsubscribe instructions in any email we send. Please note that you may be unable to unsubscribe from administrative messages without deleting your User account.
  3. We may use your personal information in order to optimize and customize your site experience as well as to identify and provide information, offers, products, or services that may be of interest to you.
  4. If you voluntarily participate in any of our surveys, contests, or promotions, we may request additional personal information from you. We may use this information to contact you about the survey, contest, or promotion, to select and notify winners, and offer you products and services or information about the Company.
  5. We may use your personal information to respond to your inquiries, provide customer service, and manage your account with the Site.
  6. We may disclose your personal information if required to do by law or to defend or prosecute a legal action.
  7. If you are a resident of a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), please refer to the section below entitled “Additional Rights of EEA Residents.”

**4\. Security  **

  1. The Site is designed to be a community based Site that provides valuable information to Users and visitors alike. Because of this, the Site may contain links to third party websites or applications. Some of these links may be submitted by Users. We do not control the third party websites or applications and can make no guarantee as to the safety or security of our visitors when they leave our Site. Please use caution when accessing any third party links.
  2. We value the security and privacy of our visitors and Users and utilize a variety of electronic and physical measures to protect your personal information from security breaches. However, we cannot guarantee the safety of your personal information and cannot guarantee that networks across which you may transmit information are secure. Therefore, the Company shall under no circumstance be liable for any inadvertent disclosure or breach of your personal information.
  3. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If we determine that we have collected personal information from a child under the age 13, we will promptly delete that personal information. If you believe that we might have any personal information from a child under the age of 13, please contact us at [info@biggerbolderbaking.com](mailto:info@biggerbolderbaking.com).
  4. We encourage you to contact us with questions or comments. You may reach us at [info@biggerbolderbaking.com](mailto:info@biggerbolderbaking.com). You may also contact us at this address if you believe the personal information we have (as it relates to you) is inaccurate or if you wish to inquire about opting out of certain collection practices.

**5\. Interest-Based Advertising**

_Advertising Privacy Statement_

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners.You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).  However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact AdThrive at info@adthrive.com. If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences icon. (Available in the EU.)

**6\. Additional Rights of EEA (European Economic Area) Residents**

If you are a resident of a country in the EEA, you have the rights, among others, to:

(i)  access your personal data

(ii)  ensure the accuracy of your personal data

(iii) the right to have us delete your personal data

(iv)  the right to restrict further processing of your personal data, and

(v)  the right to complain to a supervisory authority in your country of residence in the event that data is misused

If you believe that our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement.

You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by written notice to us addressed to the following: Kevin Kurtz, 1112 Montana Avenue #862, Santa Monica CA 90403; 424-268-8427; info@biggerbolderbaking.com.

**7\. Sale of Business or Assets**

In the event that the Site or substantially all of its assets is sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, the information we have collected about you may be one of the assets sold or merged in connection with that transaction.

**8\. Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted on the Site, with the “Effective Date” posted at the top of the Policy. We may revise and update this Privacy Policy if our practices change, as technology changes, or as we add new services or change existing ones. If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy or how we handle your personal information, or we are going to use any personal information in a manner that is materially different from that stated in our Privacy Policy at the time we collected such information, we will give you a reasonable opportunity to consent to the change. If you do not consent, your personal information will be used as agreed to under the terms of the privacy policy in effect at the time we obtained that information. By using our Site or services after the Effective Date, you are deemed to consent to our then-current privacy policy. We will use information previously obtained in accordance with the Privacy Policy in effect when the information was obtained from you.

**9\. Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the practices of this Site, please contact us at info@biggerbolderbaking.com.

Or write to us at: Kevin Kurtz, 1112 Montana Avenue #862, Santa Monica CA 90403; 424-268-8427; info@biggerbolderbaking.com.
